[
    {"question": "gold standard", "answer": "最高峰のもの；代表格、理想的なもの"},
    {"question": "kick sth off", "answer": "〜を開始する"},
    {"question": "on one's last legs", "answer": "死にかかって、壊れかかって"},
    {"question": "pluck sth out of thin air", "answer": "テキトーなことを言う"},
    {"question": "make a move", "answer": "行く"},
    {"question": "selling point", "answer": "アピールポイント、強み"},
    {"question": "all-in on sth", "answer": "〜に全てを賭けている"},
    {"question": "light at the end of the tunnel", "answer": "（困難の先にある）希望の光、目処"},
    {"question": "party animal", "answer": "パリピ、パーティが好きな人"},
    {"question": "could hear a pin drop", "answer": "シーンとしている"},
    {"question": "wordy", "answer": "（文章などが）とても長い"},
    {"question": "surefire", "answer": "（成功することが）絶対確実な"},
    {"question": "up in the air", "answer": "まだ決まっていない"},
    {"question": "worth a shot", "answer": "試す価値がある"},
    {"question": "character", "answer": "キャラが強い人、個性が強い人"},
    {"question": "sharp", "answer": "頭が良い"},
    {"question": "burning desire", "answer": "強い願望"},
    {"question": "fly on the wall", "answer": "隠れて見たり聞いたりしている人"},
    {"question": "gibberish", "answer": "意味不明な言葉"},
    {"question": "egg sb on", "answer": "〜をそそのかす"},

    {"question": "face-time", "answer": "実際に会って話す時間"},
    {"question": "pull an all-nighter", "answer": "徹夜する"},
    {"question": "leave it there", "answer": "この辺でやめておく"},
    {"question": "down-to-earth", "answer": "堅実な、現実的な"},
    {"question": "jump the gun", "answer": "早まる"},
    {"question": "back sth up", "answer": "〜を証明する、裏付ける"},
    {"question": "get a kick out of sth", "answer": "〜から快感を得る"},
    {"question": "hands down", "answer": "確実に、間違いなく"},
    {"question": "dumb sth down", "answer": "〜を分かり易くする、簡単に説明する"},
    {"question": "on the fly", "answer": "その場で"},
    {"question": "fishy", "answer": "怪しい"},
    {"question": "give or take", "answer": "大体、前後"},
    {"question": "educated guess", "answer": "（考えた上での）予測、推測"},
    {"question": "hit a wall", "answer": "壁にぶち当たる、行き詰まる"},
    {"question": "on sb's radar", "answer": "やるつもりがある、考えている"},
    {"question": "broken record", "answer": "同じことを何度も言う人"},
    {"question": "stoked", "answer": "とても嬉しい；とても楽しみな"},
    {"question": "sooner rather than later", "answer": "早めに、できるだけ早く"},
    {"question": "get one's story straight", "answer": "話を整理する"},
    {"question": "reinvent the wheel", "answer": "（無駄に）いちからやり直す"},

    {"question": "hear through the grapevine", "answer": "噂で聞く"},
    {"question": "fired up", "answer": "動揺した；怒った"},
    {"question": "crash course", "answer": "簡潔な説明；集中講義"},
    {"question": "settle in", "answer": "（新しい環境に）慣れる、順応する"},
    {"question": "worked up", "answer": "怒る、興奮する"},
    {"question": "control freak", "answer": "何にでも口を挟む人；束縛男・女"},
    {"question": "needle in a haystack", "answer": "見つけるのがほぼ不可能なもの"},
    {"question": "put up with sth", "answer": "〜を我慢する"},
    {"question": "put sb on the spot", "answer": "（困るような）難しい質問を〜にする"},
    {"question": "wasted", "answer": "酔っぱらった"},
    {"question": "ego-boosting", "answer": "モチベの上がる、自信をつけるような"},
    {"question": "carry the team", "answer": "チームを率いる"},
    {"question": "down in the dumps", "answer": "落ち込んでいる"},
    {"question": "big fan of sth", "answer": "〜が大好きな人"},
    {"question": "backfire", "answer": "裏目にでる"},
    {"question": "iffy", "answer": "微妙な；疑わしい、怪しい"},
    {"question": "go down well", "answer": "ウケが良い、評判が良い"},
    {"question": "step up", "answer": "自分が普段やること以上のことをやる"},
    {"question": "inch-perfect", "answer": "インチ（ミリ）単位で完璧な"},
    {"question": "keep one's head", "answer": "落ち着いた状態でいる、冷静さを保つ"},

    {"question": "rule of thumb", "answer": "目安、経験則"},
    {"question": "crack (sb) up", "answer": "〜を爆笑させる；爆笑する"},
    {"question": "take it the wrong way", "answer": "悪く受け取る。誤解する"},
    {"question": "give some context", "answer": "状況を説明する"},
    {"question": "drama queen", "answer": "過剰に反応する人、大げさに言う人"},
    {"question": "go all-out", "answer": "全力を尽くす、本気を出す"},
    {"question": "cover all bases", "answer": "何事にも対応できるようにする"},
    {"question": "by the book", "answer": "マニュアル人間の"},
    {"question": "think it through", "answer": "しっかりと考える"},
    {"question": "heads-up", "answer": "お知らせ"},
    {"question": "call it (a day)", "answer": "今日はもう終わりにする"},
    {"question": "in a roundabout way", "answer": "遠まわしに（言うと）"},
    {"question": "under the weather", "answer": "具合が悪い"},
    {"question": "drag ones's feet", "answer": "わざとダラダラやる、先延ばしにする"},
    {"question": "clear the ait", "answer": "わだかまりを解く"},
    {"question": "guesstimate", "answer": "テキトーな見積もり、ざっくりした予想"},
    {"question": "dig deep", "answer": "多くの努力をする"},
    {"question": "bells and whistles", "answer": "（不要な）追加的機能"},
    {"question": "spot-on", "answer": "正しい、その通りの"},
    {"question": "sb's cup of tea", "answer": "〜の好み"},

    {"question": "look sharp", "answer": "シュッとして見える"},
    {"question": "neck and neck", "answer": "接戦の、互角の"},
    {"question": "mind-numbering", "answer": "極めてつまらない"},
    {"question": "tell it like it is", "answer": "ズバズバ言う、正直に言う"},
    {"question": "game-changer", "answer": "革新的なもの、人生を変えるもの"},
    {"question": "borrow sb", "answer": "〜の助けを借りる"},
    {"question": "look up to sb", "answer": "〜を尊敬する"},
    {"question": "killing it", "answer": "調子がいい、上手にやっている"},
    {"question": "make it up as one goes along", "answer": "その場でうまくやる"},
    {"question": "bounce ideas off sb", "answer": "アイデアを〜から出してもらう"},
    {"question": "bad influences", "answer": "悪影響を与えるもの・人"},
    {"question": "pushy", "answer": "押しつけがましい"},
    {"question": "steal", "answer": "かなりお買い得なもの"},
    {"question": "wrap sth up", "answer": "〜を終わりにする"},
    {"question": "not add up", "answer": "つじつまが合わない、腑に落ちない"},
    {"question": "destroyed", "answer": "腹を立てた、怒った"},
    {"question": "not too far off (sth)", "answer": "そこまで離れていない、あと少しの"},
    {"question": "heart and soul", "answer": "中心的存在、根本的なもの"},
    {"question": "look on the bright side", "answer": "ポジティブに考える"},
    {"question": "101", "answer": "〜の基本"}
]